joeydevilla.com 2011-11-26

# Privacy Notice

**This is a privacy notice that explains the privacy practices for this site, _The Adventures of Accordion Guy in the 21st Century_.** It applies solely to information collected by this blog, and spells out the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

**The blogger, Joey deVilla, is the sole editor, author and owner of the information collected on this site.** He only has access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. He won’t sell or rent this information to anyone.

He will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted him. He will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask him not to, he may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

### Your Access to and Control Over Information

**You may opt out of any future contacts from Joey deVilla at any time.** You can do the following at any time:

  * See what data he has about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data he has about you.
  * Have him delete any data he has about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

### Security

**We take precautions to protect your information.** When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

If you feel that Joey deVilla is not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact him immediately via email at [joey@joeydevilla.com](mailto:joey@joeydevilla.com) or voice/SMS at (647) 985-5639.
